<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>learning on BlairABlake Blog</title><link>http://blairablakeblog.s3-website-ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/tags/learning/</link><description>Recent content in learning on BlairABlake Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:14:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://blairablakeblog.s3-website-ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/tags/learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MOOC recommendations</title><link>http://blairablakeblog.s3-website-ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/blog/mooc-recomendations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://blairablakeblog.s3-website-ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/blog/mooc-recomendations/</guid><description>MOOC, Massive Open Online Courses, are good friends of our learning endeavour. If you have used MOOC, you may have suprised massive amout of courses available with no money. I also suprised and confused of what course should I take. I have already used MOOC for nearly two years and learned a lot, mathematical thinking, thermodynamics, blockchain, programming, etc. In this article I will introduce you some couress I especially recommend.</description></item><item><title>The Art And Craft of Problem Solving --Book Review</title><link>http://blairablakeblog.s3-website-ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/blog/theartofproblemsolving-bookreview/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://blairablakeblog.s3-website-ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/blog/theartofproblemsolving-bookreview/</guid><description>The art and craft of problem solving by Paul Zeitz is highly recommended for those who want to get started in competitive mathematical problems as well as who are looking for the opportunities to enhance problem-solving skills in general. This book begins with the mindset of a problem-solver followed by strategies, tactics, and topic-specific chapters. This book contains too many good points to tell you right now so I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you how I changed before and after reading this book.</description></item><item><title>The Art of Multitasking</title><link>http://blairablakeblog.s3-website-ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/blog/art-of-multitasking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://blairablakeblog.s3-website-ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com/blog/art-of-multitasking/</guid><description>At the time of this writing, I was a high school student. I was eager to learn many things, mathematics, physics, chemistry, algorithm, HTML, cloud, machine learning, blockchain, etc. That amount is way out of my capacity. But my eagerness to do all these things leads to the invention of a new way of multitasking. This is what I&amp;rsquo;m gonna tell you today, the art of multitasking.
Introduction Multitasking is usually considered non-effective or simply bad, not helpful.</description></item></channel></rss>